[
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9401_MountVector",
        "Type": "MountUnlock",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": null,
        "Task": "9401_MountVector_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9401_Horse",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "9401_MountVector_Complete",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "Expansion_2023_Unlock \u0026\u0026 !9401_Befriend_Started",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 1,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9401_MountVector_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "A Change in the Wilds",
        "Description": "I've found a stained note from someone named, \"Jochi.\" It mentions something of an 'awakening,' and asks to meet him at a… stable?",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\u0026lt;continue reading\u0026gt;",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "If you wish to learn more, come find me at my stable. You'll find me in the north part of Everfall, near Walsham.\\n\\n- Jochi Khan",
        "InProgressResponse": "If you wish to learn more, come find me at my stable. You'll find me in the north part of Everfall, near Walsham.\\n\\nJochi",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Ah! You are welcome here, weary traveler. What can I offer you? Food? A place to rest?",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9401_BefriendHorse",
        "Type": "MountUnlock",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": null,
        "Task": "9401_Befriend_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9401_Horse",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "MountType_Unlock_Horse",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "Expansion_2023_Unlock",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 1,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9401_BefriendHorse_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "My Kingdom for a Horse",
        "Description": "The son of a legendary warlord has built a stable in hopes that the return of the Beast Lords will mean he can put his horse training skills to use.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"What are you hoping to accomplish?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "I knew you had a warrior's heart. Long ago, my brothers stole my inheritance from me. On that day, I swore I would prove the blood of my father flowed through my veins by taming the Takhi-- the ancient spirit horses of heaven.\\nI believe someone with a warrior's soul can now claim such a beast.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Scared? If you’re afraid, don’t go. But if you’re going, don’t be afraid.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Do you realize what we’ve done, stranger? This changes everything. Look here, spirits of my ancestors: we have brought the horse to Aeternum! \\n\\nMay the blood of my father ride forever beneath the Eternal Blue Sky!",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9401_TutorialFood",
        "Type": "MountUnlock",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": null,
        "Task": "9401_TutorialFood_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9401_Horse",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "9401_TutorialComplete",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "Expansion_2023_Unlock",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 1,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9401_Tutorial_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": false,
        "Title": "Hungry as a Horse",
        "Description": "Jochi has given you the ingredients to make Basic Mount Vittles. Craft them at any kitchen or campsite.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Don't horses eat grass?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "In the wild? Yes. But a racing horse is a special breed. With proper care, a good mount will carry you swiftly past the horizon.",
        "InProgressResponse": "A lazy rider wins few races, my friend. See to it that your horse is fed, and then we’ll talk.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Well done! Your horse looks strong and eager. But a bond is forged through many hours in the saddle.\\n\\nI have posted races at notice boards throughout the area. These will push the limits of your potential.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9401_VectorWF",
        "Type": "MountUnlock",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": null,
        "Task": "9401_VectorWF_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9402_Conman",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "9401_VectorWF_Complete",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "Expansion_2023_Unlock",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 1,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9401_VectorWF_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "Hoofing It",
        "Description": "Seek out Francois De La Rama in Weaver's Fen for additional races.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"So this Francois can teach me more about riding?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Francois is a… unique individual, from what I have come to understand. But his horsemanship is second to none, and he likes to prove that with difficult races.\\n\\nMeet with him, and you'll see what I mean.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Keep an eye on Francois when you find him in Weaver's Fen. He is talented, but he may be a little… hard to trust.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Well well, what have we here? A dusty rider on a broken mare? Or are you something more?\\n\\nI think I know who you are. Jochi's new friend, no?",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9403_VectorWolves",
        "Type": "MountUnlock",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": null,
        "Task": "9403_VectorWolves_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9403_Wolf",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "9403_VectorWolves_Complete",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "Expansion_2023_Unlock",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 1,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9403_VectorWolves_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "On the Scent",
        "Description": "François de La Rama has asked that I seek out a Varangian named Valencia Iznov, saying she might have the secret to riding wolves. I should look for her in Great Cleave and see if I can earn her trust.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"You suggest I seek out a Varangian for training?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "If you'd like to continue your training, that's exactly what you need to do. I've dealt with this Varangian before - Valencia Iznov is her name.\\n\\nShe and I didn't part ways on the umm, best of terms, but she's different than others like her.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Last time I saw her, Valencia was up in Great Cleave. I can't promise she's still there, but that's your best bet.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Stay yourself, stranger! I have no qualms about sending a wayward traveler back to their spirit shrine the hard way!",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9403_FreeWolves",
        "Type": "MountUnlock",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": null,
        "Task": "9403_FreeWolves_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9403_Wolf",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "MountType_Unlock_DireWolf",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "Expansion_2023_Unlock",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 1,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9403_FreeWolves_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "A Pack of Knaves",
        "Description": "A defector of the Varangian Order seeks aid to free a pack of dire wolves from her former compatriots.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"I sought you out to learn the secrets of wolf riding.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Then you are very naïve or very foolish. The pack is broken, and the trust of the wolves is lost. No one will be riding them again.",
        "InProgressResponse": "You tarry while our wolf-brothers languish in chains? Free the pack first, then we'll talk.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "You've freed the wolves! The natural order is restored. Look for one with a compatible spirit, and I will arrange a race to push the limits of your partnership.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9403_VectorBS",
        "Type": "MountUnlock",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": null,
        "Task": "9403_VectorBS_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9404_Record",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "9403_VectorBS_Complete",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "Expansion_2023_Unlock",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 1,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9403_VectorBS_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "Desert Dash",
        "Description": "Satiah Rahmotep is collecting a book of records of Aeternum. She has laid out truly challenging courses for those riders who would seek immortal fame.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Where can I find her?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Brimstone. I'll put the spot on your map. I've never run these races myself, but if she is to believed, they are second to none. With your wolf by your side, though, I'm sure you can master them.\\n\\nUntil we meet again, friend.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Look for Satiah out in Brimstone. I'd be more specific, but the desert heat is not for me.\\n\\nOh, and bring plenty of water for your pack.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Ah, and who is this before? Not a mirage, I should hope! Whew, the heat will get to you quick out here.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9403_VectorLions",
        "Type": "MountUnlock",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": null,
        "Task": "9403_VectorLions_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9405_Lion",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "9403_VectorLions_Complete",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "9404_T4_15_Races_Complete",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 1,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9403_VectorLions_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "A Matter of Pride",
        "Description": "Satiah Rahmotep has suggested that I seek out Zinnumun in the Elysian Wilds to further my riding training.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"Elysian Wilds. I hear it's dangerous.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "It is, and it probably seems like it is hardly the place to compete in races. But the creatures that thrive in that environment… I've heard they move like no other.",
        "InProgressResponse": "I have never been to Elysian Wilds, so I can't tell you what to expect.\\n\\nBut no one would understand how to ride an animal better than the animals themselves, and so it is there that you must go.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "What is this before me? A human deep in the territory of the Beast Lords? Perhaps I should… \\n\\nAh, but wait… something about your scent is familiar. I think I know who you are.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9405_RescueLion",
        "Type": "MountUnlock",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": null,
        "Task": "9405_RescueLion_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9405_Lion",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "MountType_Unlock_Sabretooth",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "9403_VectorLions_Complete",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 1,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9405_RescueLion_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "The Lion's Lament",
        "Description": "Zinnumun, matriarch of the Elysian lions, summons Aeternum's greatest hero to liberate her mate Kaluru from the clutches of pretender Lion Lords that seek to end the growing alliance between man and beast.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"I will free him. Where are these Zurvān??\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Their den lies just a short sprint ahead. But be cautious: they are skilled hunters. Free him, and you will have earned my bond as well.",
        "InProgressResponse": "You’re back? I don’t see my mate. Perhaps your skills as a hunter are exaggerated.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "Because of you, my darling Kaluru runs free. You have proven you have the heart of a lion. Should you require aid, call to me, and I will answer.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9401_Tour",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "9401_Tour_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 1,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9401_Race_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "Hermit's Rally",
        "Description": "Plot a route to the finish line and get there within the time limit.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "Read Race Rules",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Fast traveling will disqualify you from the trial. If your time expires the trial will reset. You may only have one trial at a time.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Fast traveling will disqualify you from the trial. If you fail the trial will reset. You may only have one trial at a time.\\n\\nBest get back to the starting line, time waits for no man.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "You've completed the race posted. Try returning later for more tours.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9403_Tour",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "9403_Tour_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 2,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9403_Race_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@9403_Tour_title",
        "Description": "Get to the destination within the time limit.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9403_Tour_start",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9403_Tour_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "Race from ___ to ___ if you dare, adventurer! Finish in \u0026lt;par time\u0026gt; if you want my respect. Now, ride like the wind!\\n\\n\u0026lt;font face=\"lyshineui/fonts/Nimbus_semibold.font\" color=\"#DDDDDD\"\u0026gt;Recommended Riding Level 50]",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9403_Tour_complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9401_Rally",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "9401_Rally_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 1,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9401_Race_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@9401_Rally_title",
        "Description": "Reach each checkpoint then cross the finish line within the time limit.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "Read Time Trial Rules",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Fast traveling will disqualify you from the trial. If you fail the trial will reset. You may only have one trial at a time.\\n\\nBest get back to the starting line, time waits for no man.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Fast traveling will disqualify you from the trial. If you fail the trial will reset. You may only have one trial at a time.\\n\\nBest get back to the starting line, time waits for no man.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "You've completed the race posted. Try returning later for more rallies.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9402_Rally",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "9402_Rally_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 2,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9402_Race_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@9402_Rally_title",
        "Description": "@9402_Rally_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9402_Rally_start",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9402_Rally_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9402_Rally_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9402_Rally_complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9404_Rally",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": false,
        "Task": "9404_Rally_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": 2,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9404_Race_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@9403_Rally_title",
        "Description": "@9403_Rally_description",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9403_Rally_start",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@9403_Rally_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@9403_Rally_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@9403_Rally_complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "EF_Tour_0",
        "Type": "MountRace",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "9401_FirstRace_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9401_Horse",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "EF_Tour_0_Complete",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "MountType_Unlock_Horse",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "EF_Tour_0_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "Hermit's Rally",
        "Description": "Plot a route to the finish line and get there within the time limit.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"How do I strengthen the bond with my horse?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "My people learn to ride at age two, and start racing at age six. I hope you're at least as skilled as our children. Let's find out.\\n\\nI have arranged a practice race for you. Head to the starting line to test your skills.",
        "InProgressResponse": "You have already done the impossible, my friend. Do not begin to doubt yourself now. It is no matter if you fall seven times, so long as you have the strength to rise eight.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "I knew you had it in you! Push your limits and your skills will continue to grow.\\n\\nNow that the bond between man and beast has been rekindled, you'll find challenges from other racers. Be prepared.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "EF_Rally_1",
        "Type": "MountRace",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "EF_Rally_1_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "EF_Rally_1_Complete",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "EF_Rally_1_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "Radiant Hills Rally",
        "Description": "Reach each checkpoint then cross the finish line within the time limit.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "Read More",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Wend your way up and down over the glowing hills of Everfall. You will dash by fortifications and spiked defenses. The sun is out and it's a beautiful day for a skirmish.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Fast traveling will disqualify you from the trial. If you fail the trial will reset. You may only have one trial at a time.\\n\\nBest get back to the starting line, time waits for no man.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "You've completed the race posted. Try returning later for more rallies.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "EF_Rally_2",
        "Type": "MountRace",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "EF_Rally_2_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "EF_Rally_2_Complete",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "EF_Rally_2_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "Stolen Shores Rally",
        "Description": "Reach each checkpoint then cross the finish line within the time limit.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "Read More",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Descend into the pirateship graveyard of Stolen Shores, weaving in and out of the wreckage of fools who sought glory.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Fast traveling will disqualify you from the trial. If you fail the trial will reset. You may only have one trial at a time.\\n\\nBest get back to the starting line, time waits for no man.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "You've completed the race posted. Try returning later for more rallies.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "EF_Tour_1",
        "Type": "MountRace",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "EF_Tour_1_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "EF_Tour_1_Complete",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "EF_Tour_1_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "King's Road Tour",
        "Description": "Plot a route to the finish line and get there within the time limit.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "Read More",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Follow the road south through lush forests and busy trade routes onward to the ivory walls of Artorias's court.\\n\\nEnds at Prydwen Castle in Monarch's Bluffs.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Fast traveling will disqualify you from the trial. If you fail the trial will reset. You may only have one trial at a time.\\n\\nBest get back to the starting line, time waits for no man.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "You've completed the race posted. Try returning later for more tours.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "EF_Tour_2",
        "Type": "MountRace",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "EF_Tour_2_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "EF_Tour_2_Complete",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "EF_Tour_2_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "Dogma Tour",
        "Description": "Plot a route to the finish line and get there within the time limit.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "Read More",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Travel south from the Syndicate's shadowy enclave to past a bridge of the damned and end at the glimmering temple of the Covenant.\\n\\nEnds at Covenant Shrine in Everfall.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Fast traveling will disqualify you from the trial. If you fail the trial will reset. You may only have one trial at a time.\\n\\nBest get back to the starting line, time waits for no man.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "You've completed the race posted. Try returning later for more tours.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "EF_Tour_3",
        "Type": "MountRace",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "EF_Tour_3_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "EF_Tour_3_Complete",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "EF_Tour_3_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "Ghosts and Groves Tour",
        "Description": "Plot a route to the finish line and get there within the time limit.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "Read More",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Dash through ancient groves over the roads that many would be heroes once trod.\\n\\nEnds at Calvary Hamlet in Brightwood.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Fast traveling will disqualify you from the trial. If you fail the trial will reset. You may only have one trial at a time.\\n\\nBest get back to the starting line, time waits for no man.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "You've completed the race posted. Try returning later for more tours.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "WF_Rally_1",
        "Type": "MountRace",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "WF_Rally_1_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "WF_Rally_1_Complete",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "9401_T1_5_Races_Complete",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "WF_Rally_1_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "Vega Bridge Rally",
        "Description": "Reach each checkpoint then cross the finish line within the time limit.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "Read More",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Travel along and under the majestic Vega Bridge. Take care on the boardwalks and make your way to Fenton without being caught by the restless dead.\\n\\nEnds at the bridge south of Fenton.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Fast traveling will disqualify you from the trial. If you fail the trial will reset. You may only have one trial at a time.\\n\\nBest get back to the starting line, time waits for no man.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "You've completed the race posted. Try returning later for more rallies.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "WF_Rally_2",
        "Type": "MountRace",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "WF_Rally_2_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "WF_Rally_2_Complete",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "9401_T1_5_Races_Complete",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "WF_Rally_2_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "Diver's Bluff Rally",
        "Description": "Reach each checkpoint then cross the finish line within the time limit.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "Read More",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Learn the acrobatic triumph of high diving if you dare. Watch out for ghosts and find a perch just after the windmill. Only the most daring of smugglers dive  to the water below.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Fast traveling will disqualify you from the trial. If you fail the trial will reset. You may only have one trial at a time.\\n\\nBest get back to the starting line, time waits for no man.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "You've completed the race posted. Try returning later for more rallies.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "WF_Tour_1",
        "Type": "MountRace",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "WF_Tour_1_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "WF_Tour_1_Complete",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "9401_T1_5_Races_Complete",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "WF_Tour_1_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "Iron Rose Tour",
        "Description": "Plot a route to the finish line and get there within the time limit.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "Read More",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "The doomed mercenary company used this path to build endurance. Though they have all but perished, this road holds their memory.\\n\\nEnds at Iron Rose Shrine in Windsward.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Fast traveling will disqualify you from the trial. If you fail the trial will reset. You may only have one trial at a time.\\n\\nBest get back to the starting line, time waits for no man.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "You've completed the race posted. Try returning later for more tours.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "WF_Tour_2",
        "Type": "MountRace",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "WF_Tour_2_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "WF_Tour_2_Complete",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "9401_T1_5_Races_Complete",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "WF_Tour_2_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "Thieves' Way Tour",
        "Description": "Plot a route to the finish line and get there within the time limit.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "Read More",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "A path for stealing both gold and hearts. Take care plotting your course else you may find yourself lost like so many souls who have chosen the thieves' way.\\n\\nEnds at Syndicate Shrine in Everfall.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Fast traveling will disqualify you from the trial. If you fail the trial will reset. You may only have one trial at a time.\\n\\nBest get back to the starting line, time waits for no man.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "You've completed the race posted. Try returning later for more tours.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "WF_Tour_3",
        "Type": "MountRace",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "WF_Tour_3_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "WF_Tour_3_Complete",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "9401_T1_5_Races_Complete",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "WF_Tour_3_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "Flood and Folly Tour",
        "Description": "Plot a route to the finish line and get there within the time limit.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "Read More",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Forge a path through the flooded villages. The windmills still spin though their citizens have long gone Lost. Any road out of the swamp is the right road.\\n\\nEnds at the bridge south of Fenton.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Fast traveling will disqualify you from the trial. If you fail the trial will reset. You may only have one trial at a time.\\n\\nBest get back to the starting line, time waits for no man.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "You've completed the race posted. Try returning later for more tours.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "GC_Rally_1",
        "Type": "MountRace",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "GC_Rally_1_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "GC_Rally_1_Complete",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "9402_T2_10_Races_Complete",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "GC_Rally_1_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "Temple of Tears Rally",
        "Description": "Reach each checkpoint then cross the finish line within the time limit.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "Read More",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "The waters hold secrets just as the snows hold silence.\\n\\nEnds at Riven Anvil in Great Cleave.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Fast traveling will disqualify you from the trial. If you fail the trial will reset. You may only have one trial at a time.\\n\\nBest get back to the starting line, time waits for no man.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "You've completed the race posted. Try returning later for more rallies.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "GC_Rally_2",
        "Type": "MountRace",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "GC_Rally_2_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "GC_Rally_2_Complete",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "9402_T2_10_Races_Complete",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "GC_Rally_2_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "Downhill Rush Rally",
        "Description": "Reach each checkpoint then cross the finish line within the time limit.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "Read More",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Run like a cannonball down a rolling mountainside under threat of shrieking death.\\n\\nEnds at Caer Dun in Brightwood.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Fast traveling will disqualify you from the trial. If you fail the trial will reset. You may only have one trial at a time.\\n\\nBest get back to the starting line, time waits for no man.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "You've completed the race posted. Try returning later for more rallies.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "GC_Tour_1",
        "Type": "MountRace",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "GC_Tour_1_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "GC_Tour_1_Complete",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "9402_T2_10_Races_Complete",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "GC_Tour_1_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "Wolf's Bane Tour",
        "Description": "Plot a route to the finish line and get there within the time limit.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "Read More",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Dash out of the snowy reaches of Great Cleave to the green hills of Edengrove.\\n\\nEnds at Fabhcon shrine.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Fast traveling will disqualify you from the trial. If you fail the trial will reset. You may only have one trial at a time.\\n\\nBest get back to the starting line, time waits for no man.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "You've completed the race posted. Try returning later for more tours.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "GC_Tour_2",
        "Type": "MountRace",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "GC_Tour_2_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "GC_Tour_2_Complete",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "9402_T2_10_Races_Complete",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "GC_Tour_2_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "Ancient Alley Tour",
        "Description": "Plot a route to the finish line and get there within the time limit.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "Read More",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Dash down the mountainside and south to an unsuspecting Varangian fortress.\\n\\nEnds at Pennine shrine in Brightwood.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Fast traveling will disqualify you from the trial. If you fail the trial will reset. You may only have one trial at a time.\\n\\nBest get back to the starting line, time waits for no man.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "You've completed the race posted. Try returning later for more tours.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "GC_Tour_3",
        "Type": "MountRace",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "GC_Tour_3_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "GC_Tour_3_Complete",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "9402_T2_10_Races_Complete",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "GC_Tour_3_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "Snows and Spirits Tour",
        "Description": "Plot a route to the finish line and get there within the time limit.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "Read More",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Stay true on the path and follow it south through snow and silence.\\n\\nEnds at Wolfsegg Shrine in Brightwood.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Fast traveling will disqualify you from the trial. If you fail the trial will reset. You may only have one trial at a time.\\n\\nBest get back to the starting line, time waits for no man.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "You've completed the race posted. Try returning later for more tours.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "BS_Rally_1",
        "Type": "MountRace",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "BS_Rally_1_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "BS_Rally_1_Complete",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "9403_T3_15_Races_Complete",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "BS_Rally_1_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "Rally of the Gods",
        "Description": "Reach each checkpoint then cross the finish line within the time limit.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "Read More",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "The great pyramid, the mercury pools, and the settlement - the ancient gods look over everything in eternal splendor.\\n\\nEnds at New Corsica in Brimstone Sands.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Fast traveling will disqualify you from the trial. If you fail the trial will reset. You may only have one trial at a time.\\n\\nBest get back to the starting line, time waits for no man.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "You've completed the race posted. Try returning later for more rallies.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "BS_Rally_2",
        "Type": "MountRace",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "BS_Rally_2_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "BS_Rally_2_Complete",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "9403_T3_15_Races_Complete",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "BS_Rally_2_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "Skysong Rally",
        "Description": "Reach each checkpoint then cross the finish line within the time limit.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "Read More",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Make your way through gorgeous flora, a spirit filled graveyard, and a fortress of the corrupted.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Fast traveling will disqualify you from the trial. If you fail the trial will reset. You may only have one trial at a time.\\n\\nBest get back to the starting line, time waits for no man.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "You've completed the race posted. Try returning later for more rallies.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "BS_Tour_1",
        "Type": "MountRace",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "BS_Tour_1_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "BS_Tour_1_Complete",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "9403_T3_15_Races_Complete",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "BS_Tour_1_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "Pilgrimage of Light Tour",
        "Description": "Plot a route to the finish line and get there within the time limit.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "Read More",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Take in the light drenched cliffs of Ebonscale Reach as you gallop across sparkling sands and serene skylines.\\n\\nEnds at Pilgrim's Rest.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Fast traveling will disqualify you from the trial. If you fail the trial will reset. You may only have one trial at a time.\\n\\nBest get back to the starting line, time waits for no man.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "You've completed the race posted. Try returning later for more tours.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "BS_Tour_2",
        "Type": "MountRace",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "BS_Tour_2_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "BS_Tour_2_Complete",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "9403_T3_15_Races_Complete",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "BS_Tour_2_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "Four Seasons Tour",
        "Description": "Plot a route to the finish line and get there within the time limit.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "Read More",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Ride through landscapes painted with summer, winter, fall, and spring.\\n\\nEnds at the Shrine of Orion in Mourningdale.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Fast traveling will disqualify you from the trial. If you fail the trial will reset. You may only have one trial at a time.\\n\\nBest get back to the starting line, time waits for no man.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "You've completed the race posted. Try returning later for more tours.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "BS_Tour_3",
        "Type": "MountRace",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "BS_Tour_3_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "BS_Tour_3_Complete",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "9403_T3_15_Races_Complete",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "BS_Tour_3_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "Barrens and Bogs Tour",
        "Description": "Plot a route to the finish line and get there within the time limit.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "Read More",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Use your growing knowledge of the northern courses to plot a route to Reekwater.\\n\\nEnds at Siren's Run.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Fast traveling will disqualify you from the trial. If you fail the trial will reset. You may only have one trial at a time.\\n\\nBest get back to the starting line, time waits for no man.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "You've completed the race posted. Try returning later for more tours.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "EW_Rally_1",
        "Type": "MountRace",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "EW_Rally_1_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "EW_Rally_1_Complete",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "9404_T4_15_Races_Complete",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "EW_Rally_1_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "Emerald Run Rally",
        "Description": "Reach each checkpoint then cross the finish line within the time limit.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "Read More",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Descend into the wild greens of Beast Lord stomping grounds, leap beyond the clutch of hungry teeth, and make your way back to Last Light.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Fast traveling will disqualify you from the trial. If you fail the trial will reset. You may only have one trial at a time.\\n\\nBest get back to the starting line, time waits for no man.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "You've completed the race posted. Try returning later for more rallies.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "EW_Rally_2",
        "Type": "MountRace",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "EW_Rally_2_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "EW_Rally_2_Complete",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "9404_T4_15_Races_Complete",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "EW_Rally_2_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "Hanging Gardens Rally",
        "Description": "Reach each checkpoint then cross the finish line within the time limit.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "Read More",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Dash through green rolling hills and the tunnels of Tempestas Custodia for the ultimate test of your agility.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Fast traveling will disqualify you from the trial. If you fail the trial will reset. You may only have one trial at a time.\\n\\nBest get back to the starting line, time waits for no man.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "You've completed the race posted. Try returning later for more rallies.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "EW_Tour_1",
        "Type": "MountRace",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "EW_Tour_1_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "EW_Tour_1_Complete",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "9404_T4_15_Races_Complete",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "EW_Tour_1_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "Warrior's Reprise Tour",
        "Description": "Plot a route to the finish line and get there within the time limit.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "Read More",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Ride back to where your journey with beastkind began.\\n\\nEnds at Jochi's Stable in Everfall.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Fast traveling will disqualify you from the trial. If you fail the trial will reset. You may only have one trial at a time.\\n\\nBest get back to the starting line, time waits for no man.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "You've completed the race posted. Try returning later for more tours.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "EW_Tour_2",
        "Type": "MountRace",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "EW_Tour_2_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "EW_Tour_2_Complete",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "9404_T4_15_Races_Complete",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "EW_Tour_2_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "Island Tour",
        "Description": "Plot a route to the finish line and get there within the time limit.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "Read More",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Island Tour - Test your true mettle with the fearlessness of a lion.\\n\\nEnds at Place of Pillars in Brimstone Sands.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Fast traveling will disqualify you from the trial. If you fail the trial will reset. You may only have one trial at a time.\\n\\nBest get back to the starting line, time waits for no man.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "You've completed the race posted. Try returning later for more tours.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "EW_Tour_3",
        "Type": "MountRace",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "EW_Tour_3_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "EW_Tour_3_Complete",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "9404_T4_15_Races_Complete",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "EW_Tour_3_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "Sands and Storms Tour",
        "Description": "Plot a route to the finish line and get there within the time limit.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "Read More",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Ponder the mysteries of Aeternum through to a final storming chaos.\\n\\nEnds at Shrine of Orion in Mourningdale.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Fast traveling will disqualify you from the trial. If you fail the trial will reset. You may only have one trial at a time.\\n\\nBest get back to the starting line, time waits for no man.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "You've completed the race posted. Try returning later for more tours.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9401_Races",
        "Type": "MountUnlock",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "9401_Races_Quest",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9401_Horse",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "9401_T1_5_Races_Complete",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "9401_TutorialComplete",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9401_T1_5_Races_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "Warrior's Path Circuit",
        "Description": "Jochi Khan has asked me to build a bond between me and my horse by completing the Warrior's Path Circuit.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"And these races will do that?\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "They will. The times I've posted are challenging, but pushing youself and your steed to beat those will forge trust between the two of you.\\n\\nGood luck.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Don't be intimidated by the tracks. They are meant to be difficult, but that difficulty will make you both stronger.\\n\\nShow me you can do them.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "You've returned! And I can already see a stronger rider before me.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9402_Races",
        "Type": "MountUnlock",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "9402_Races_Quest",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9402_Conman",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "9402_T2_10_Races_Complete",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "9401_VectorWF_Complete",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9402_T2_10_Races_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "Smuggler's Ring Circuit",
        "Description": "Francois has posted 5 new races around Weaver's Fen. Complete them to improve your riding skills.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"I'll accept that challenge.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "So I have heard. But Jochi is a romantic in love with the idea of rider and mount as one.\\n\\nI live under no such delusions. I only care what you can bring to the table. So show me. I want to see what you can do.",
        "InProgressResponse": "You can quit if you would like. These tracks are not for the faint of heart.\\n\\nI suspect you are not the kind to do that, though.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "You ride like the wind, stranger. I admit, I did not expect to lose. C’est la vie… \\n\\nI have heard tales of Varangian knights astride great wolves. Can you imagine such a thing? Find them, and perhaps you can learn their secret.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9403_Races",
        "Type": "MountUnlock",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "9403_Races_Quest",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9403_Wolf",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "9403_T3_15_Races_Complete",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "9403_VectorWolves_Complete",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9403_T3_15_Races_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "White Howl Circuit",
        "Description": "In order to better bond with my wolf, I need to run the circuit set up by Valencia Iznov.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"I could race with them to show what I've learned.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "That would certainly work. The pack is swift and strong, and showing the wolf that you can guide them would prove you are capable.\\n\\nI have set up a series of challenging races near here that you can use for that purpose. Come back to me when you've finished them.",
        "InProgressResponse": "My races are difficult, but they are meant to be. The wolves need to know your strength.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "You and your wolf are now of one spirit. But further challenges will strengthen your bond. I have heard of a woman who seeks out the island's greatest champions. Perhaps it is time your legend grows.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9404_Races",
        "Type": "MountUnlock",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "9404_Races_Quest",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9404_Record",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "9404_T4_15_Races_Complete",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "9403_VectorBS_Complete",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9404_T4_15_Races_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "Codex Aeternum Circuit",
        "Description": "Challenge the race times set by Satiah Rahmotep, and prove you can beat the times set by the ancients.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"I hear you found courses once thought lost to time.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "I have! And those that lived here before certainly expected much from their competitors. From what I have heard, though, you are not one to be underestimated.\\n\\nI'd like to see you challenge the times of the ancient ones.",
        "InProgressResponse": "I know those times seem difficult, but remember, they were set by those whose legends have lasted for lifetimes. Prove that you deserve to stand among them.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "You've come back! And I cannot believe it, you've beaten times that have stood for milennia!\\n\\nOh, I knew there was something special about you… I can't wait to compose a story about this!",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "9405_Races",
        "Type": "MountUnlock",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "9405_Races_Quest",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9405_Lion",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "9405_T5_15_Races_Complete",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "9405_RescueLion_Complete",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "9405_T5_15_Races_Success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "Beast Lord Circuit",
        "Description": "Zinnumun has set me to train on the same courses they use to teach their young. I must show I can match or beat the times set by hunting lions.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "\"I've come to learn to be a rider without peer.\"",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "I see… well, as you have proven yourself on many occasions to be a friend of our kind, we will grant you this favor.\\n\\nThere is no greater teacher than experience, though, and that is what I will give you.",
        "InProgressResponse": "We expect much from our young. If you are going to stride alongside lions, you must show you can keep up with the pride.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "You're come back, every bit as capable as a member of our tribe.\\n\\nI commend you, friend human. There are few of your kind that could accomplish what you have. Go forth, and use your bonds wisely.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "MountRace_ScaleTest_1",
        "Type": "MountRace",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "MountRace_ScaleTest_1_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "Barrens and Bogs Tour II",
        "Description": "Plot a route to the finish line and get there within the time limit.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9403_Tour_start",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Fast traveling will disqualify you from the trial. If your time expires the trial will reset. You may only have one trial at a time.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Fast traveling will disqualify you from the trial. If you fail the trial will reset. You may only have one trial at a time.\\n\\nBest get back to the starting line, time waits for no man.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "You've completed the race posted. Try returning later for more tours.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "MountRace_ScaleTest_2",
        "Type": "MountRace",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "MountRace_ScaleTest_2_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "Barrens and Bogs Tour II",
        "Description": "Plot a route to the finish line and get there within the time limit.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9403_Tour_start",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Fast traveling will disqualify you from the trial. If your time expires the trial will reset. You may only have one trial at a time.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Fast traveling will disqualify you from the trial. If you fail the trial will reset. You may only have one trial at a time.\\n\\nBest get back to the starting line, time waits for no man.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "You've completed the race posted. Try returning later for more tours.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "MountRace_ScaleTest_1_Short",
        "Type": "MountRace",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "MountRace_ScaleTest_1_Short_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "Barrens and Bogs Tour II",
        "Description": "Plot a route to the finish line and get there within the time limit.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9403_Tour_start",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Fast traveling will disqualify you from the trial. If your time expires the trial will reset. You may only have one trial at a time.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Fast traveling will disqualify you from the trial. If you fail the trial will reset. You may only have one trial at a time.\\n\\nBest get back to the starting line, time waits for no man.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "You've completed the race posted. Try returning later for more tours.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "MountRace_ScaleTest_2_Short",
        "Type": "MountRace",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": true,
        "Task": "MountRace_ScaleTest_2_Short_Container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": null,
        "SuccessGameEventId": "",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": "",
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "Barrens and Bogs Tour II",
        "Description": "Plot a route to the finish line and get there within the time limit.",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@9403_Tour_start",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "Fast traveling will disqualify you from the trial. If your time expires the trial will reset. You may only have one trial at a time.",
        "InProgressResponse": "Fast traveling will disqualify you from the trial. If you fail the trial will reset. You may only have one trial at a time.\\n\\nBest get back to the starting line, time waits for no man.",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "Complete the Quest",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "You've completed the race posted. Try returning later for more tours.",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    }
]
